<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>J. B. Sousa on João Brogueira de Sousa</title>
    <link>https://jbsousa.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in J. B. Sousa on João Brogueira de Sousa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://jbsousa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jbsousa.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jbsousa.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: foo@xyz.com Phone: +91-123123 Mailing Address 221B, Baker Street
London
United Kingdom
Social Facebook Twitter Google+ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>J. B. Sousa</title>
      <link>https://jbsousa.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jbsousa.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Junior Researcher in Economics at Nova School of Business and Economics, in Carcavelos (Portugal).
email: joao.sousa@novasbe.pt
Working papers On the Design of a European Unemployment Insurance System (2023, conditionally accepted at the European Economic Review) [working paper], with Árpád Ábrahám, Ramon Marimon and Lukas Mayr Work in progress Schooling and Lifetime Labor Supply (new draft soon) [slides]
Modeling Wealth and Income Inequality: Implications for Optimal Taxation (draft coming soon), with Pedro Brinca, Hans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://jbsousa.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jbsousa.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Appointments Junior Researcher, Nova School of Business and Economics, 2021 - Invited Assistant Professor, Católica Lisbon School of Business and Economics, 2019-2021 Postdoctoral Reseacher, Católica Lisbon School of Business and Economics, 2019-2021 Education Ph.D. in Economics, European University Institute, 2018 M.Res. in Economics, European University Institute, 2015 M.Sc. in Economics, Universidade Católica Portuguesa, 2013 Licenciatura in Aerospace Engineering, Instituto Superior Técnico, 2010 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
